Arthur J. Pulos Papers
Arthur J. Pulos Papers
- Design practice/office records
  - Swingline Company
    - SW-38 Omni desk manual stapler, 1980; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SW-39 Omni 113 stapler, 1980; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SW-40 Plastic spring action stapler, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SW-41 Staple box, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SW-42 Burster 6360, 1981; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SW-43 Omni revision, 1983 (Box 16)
    - SW-59 Foreign applications, 1978-80 (Box 16)
    - SW-100 Color and graphics, 1979-80 (Box 16)
    - SW-Gen General consulting services, 1977-83 (Box 16)
    - SWA-1 Stapler between ace and cadet, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SWA-2 Stripped down Ace Liner (cancelled) (Box 16)
    - SWA-3 New half strip machine, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SWA-4 Low cost 404, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SWA-5 Staple remover, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SWA-6 New line concepts, 1980; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SWA-7 Omni electric stapler, 1980; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SWA-8 Middle line half & full strip, 1980; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SWA-9 Omni electric desk stapler, 1980; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SWA-10 Copy center unit, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SWA-11 Cap for 99 plier, 1980-81; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SWA-12 New full strip stapler, 1981; includes slides (Box 16)
  - Syracuse China Corporation
    - SC-1 Facet giftware, 1963-64 (Box 16)
    - SC-2 Atlantic city exhibition, 1961-62 (Box 16)
    - SC-3 Dinnerware, 1963 (Box 16)
  - Syracuse Electronics
    - SE-1 GFCI duplex outlet, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Syracuse University
    - SY-2 Conference table, 1961 (Box 16)
    - SY-3 Cartography table, 1961 (Box 16)
    - SY-4 Color preference set, 1967 (Box 16)
    - SU-10 Graduate mark, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SU-11 Gimbel's display, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Syracuse Univ. Energy Display, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Syracuse Univ. Graduate Studies
    - Graphics, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Syracuse Univ. Research Corp.
    - SURC-1 Presentation, 1965-66 (Box 16)
    - SURC-2 Corporate identity/letterhead, 1966 (Box 16)
  - Syracuse Urban Cultural Parks
    - SY-1 Display panels, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Systems Planning Associates
    - SP-1 Graphic program, 1969-70 (Box 16)
  - Vega Industries
    - VE-2 Vega extrusion project, 1962; includes photographs, slides (Box 16)
    - VE-3 Fireplace, 1960; includes photographs, slides (Box 16)
    - VE-5 (Box 16)
    - VE-8 (Box 16)
    - VE-9 5900 Fireplace (Box 16)
  - Victor Business Products
    - VI-1 Business computer, 1981; includes photographs, slides (Box 16)
    - VI-2 Calculator colors, 1981 (Box 16)
    - VI-3 Victor printer, 1981 (Box 16)
    - VI-4 Computer logos, 1981; includes slides (Box 16)
    - VI-5 Printer painting, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Welch Allyn, Incorporated
    - WE-1 Recharger, 1958-59; includes photographs, slides (Box 17)
    - WE-2 Instrument carrying case, 1959 (Box 17)
    - WE-3 Rechargeable flashlight, 1959; includes slides (Box 17)
    - WE-4 Battery handle redesign, 1960 (Box 17)
    - WE-5 Penlight clip, 1959; includes photographs (Box 17)
    - WE-6 Otoscope head, 1960 (Box 17)
    - WE-7 Hemoglobinometer, 1961 (Box 17)
    - WE-8 Corporate design program, 1961 (Box 17)
    - WE-9 Display, 1961-62 (Box 17)
    - WE-12 #129 Opthalmoscope, #229 otoscope, 1965-69; includes photographs, slides (Box 17)
    - WE-15 "C" instruments, 1969-72; includes photographs (Box 17)
    - WE-16 Comb. otoscope/opthalmoscope unit, 1969-73 (Box 17)
    - WE-17 Retinoscope, 1969-76; includes photographs (Box 17)
    - WE-18 Disposable instruments, 1970-74; includes slides (Box 17)
    - WE-20 Vaginal scope, 1973 (Box 17)
    - WE-21 Battery charger, 1973; includes photographs (Box 17)
    - WE-22 3.5 Volt instrument colors, 1974 (Box 17)
    - WE-23 Optical reader, 1973-74 (Box 17)
    - WE-24 Rechargeable battery handle, 1974 (Box 17)
    - WE-25 Endoscope, 1981-82; includes slides (Box 17)
    - WE-26 Video illuminator/processor, 1982; includes slides (Box 17)
    - WE-27 Audiometer, 1982-83; includes photographs, slides (Box 17)
    - WE-28 Endoscope connector, 1982 (Box 17)
    - WE-29 Video endoscope cart, 1982 (Box 17)
    - WE-30 Corporate identity program, 1982; includes photographs, slides (Box 17)
    - WE-31 Blood pressure meter, 1982-83; includes slides (Box 17)
    - WE-32 Endoscope knob, 1982 (Box 17)
    - WE-33 Tympanometer, 1984; includes slides (Box 17)
    - WE-34 Lite set, 1984 (Box 17)
    - WE-35 Tympanometer head redesign, 1984 (Box 17)
    - WE-G Borescope, 1973 (Box 17)
    - WE-Gen Retainer, 1971-73 (Box 17)
  - Non-client office projects
    - Christmas card PDA, 1983 (Box 17)
    - ET-1 Press type guide, 1983 (Box 17)
    - ET-2 Slide viewer, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Federal Design Assembly
    - FE-1 Prismascope, 1975 (Box 17)
  - French Furniture Competition, 1982 (Box 17)
  - McCormick Laboratories (Box 17)
  - New England Museum Of Sports
    - NE-1 Logo, 1980 (Box 17)
  - Office projects
    - 1976 Office brochure (Box 17)
    - OF-1 Exhibit for IPI (Box 17)
    - OF-2 Garage (Box 17)
    - OF-4 Christmas card (Box 17)
    - OF-9 Rosenthal trademark, 1969 (Box 17)
    - OF-16 IDSA, 1970-72 (Box 17)
    - OF-30 Alcoa awards, 1969-71 (Box 17)
    - OF-37 Account development, 1971-73 (Box 17)
    - OF-38 Humanics project, 1970 (Box 17)
    - OF-41 "Fit of Things, 1971 (Box 17)
    - OF-42 Urban image, 1971 (Box 17)
    - OF-44 Smithsonian exhib. "Design Is...", 1971 (Box 17)
    - OF-45 Smithsonian exhib. "Shared Environ.", 1971 (Box 17)
    - OF-47 League of Women Voters letterhead, 1971 (Box 17)
    - OF-50 Promotional brochures, 1974-75 (Box 17)
    - OF-51 Annual design review, 1974 (Box 17)
    - OF-54 Christmas card - PDA, 1974 (Box 17)
    - OF-55 Office graphics, 1974 (Box 17)
    - OF-56 1980 Olympics research, 1974 (Box 17)
    - OF-57 Aviation center proposal, 1975 (Box 17)
    - OF-58 Christmas card, 1976 (Box 17)
    - OF-59 Client development, 1977 (Box 17)
    - OF-60 Commuter airlines development, 1977-78 (Box 17)
    - OF-61 Special projects research, 1981 (Box 17)
    - OF-62 PDA brochure, 1982 (Box 17)
    - OF-63 Client contact/airplane graphics, 1983-84 (Box 17)
    - OF-64 Proposed "Cube" game, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Office graphics- PDA
    - PDA booklet (Box 17)
    - PDA Promotional brochure, 1982 (Box 17)
    - PDA Business cards, 1967-74 (Box 17)
    - PDA Letterheads, graphics, 1967-74 (Box 17)
  - Owens-Corning seminar, 1974 (Box 17)
  - Plastics World, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Retirement announcement - A. Pulos, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Rockwell promotional booklet (Box 17)
  - Sullivan County Community College, 1972 (Box 17)
  - United Nations Association, 1971 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous PDA slides (Box 17)
  - Auxiliary flat files / oversize (Box 17)
  - Piper Aircraft Corporation
    - Presentation plates (Box 17)
    - B presentation plates (Box 17)
  - Dictaphone Corporation/Satellite Business Systems
    - C Foam Core, Fold-out Mock-ups (Box 17)
- Personal records
  - 1958-1976 (Box A)
  - 1977-1983 (Box B)
- Business records
  - Business certificate (Box C)
  - Client development (Box C)
  - Employee work agreements (Box C)
  - Personal time records and calendars (Box C)
- 2000 accession
  - Correspondence
    - A – General Correspondence (Box 1)
    - A – General Telephone Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Airline Litigation (Box 1)
    - Alpha Rho Chi (Box 1)
    - American Center for Design (Box 1)
    - American Craft (Box 1)
    - American Craft Council (Box 1)
    - Antique Mfg. Products (Box 1)
    - Arango Design Foundation (Box 1)
    - Arafat – 1969 (Box 1)
    - Arch. of American Art (Box 1)
    - Archives of American Art (Box 1)
    - Archives – IDSA (Box 1)
    - Archives S.U. (Box 1)
    - Argentina (Box 1)
    - Arts and Crafts Movement (Box 1)
    - Associated Artists of Pittsburgh (Box 1)
    - Athenaeum Art – Victoria Matrango (Box 1)
    - Australia (Box 1)
    - Australia 1977- 1981 (Box 1)
    - Austria (Box 1)
    - B - General (Box 2)
    - Beckman Ronald (Box 2)
    - Blaich, Robert Ian (Box 2)
    - Bodiu S. (Metalsmith Magazine) (Box 2)
    - Brazil (Box 2)
    - Bulgaria (Box 2)
    - Business Week (Box 2)
    - C - General (Box 2)
    - Canada (Box 2)
    - Carnegie Mellon Univ. Bd. Advisors Oct 26-27 (Box 2)
    - Chicago (Box 2)
    - Chicago Italian Trade Commission June 1990 (Box 2)
    - Chicago June 1990 (Box 2)
    - Chicago Art Institute (Box 2)
    - China (Box 2)
    - Clemin Shaw Book of Plastics (Box 2)
    - CMU Advisory Board (Box 2)
    - CMU Dept. of Design (Box 2)
    - CMU Design Advisory Board (Box 3)
    - CMU + PGH AP Personal (Box 3)
    - Colombia (Box 3)
    - Collections (Box 3)
    - Compasso D' Oro (Box 3)
    - Competitions (Box 3)
    - Contemporary Designers (Box 3)
    - Coolidge SPNEA (Box 3)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Bel Geddes Talk 3/8/94 (Box 3)
    - Corning (Box 3)
    - Corporate Design Foundation (Box 3)
    - Costa Rica (Box 3)
    - Cuba (Box 3)
    - Cultural Forum (Box 3)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box 3)
    - D - General (Box 4)
    - Dallas Exhibit + Panel 9/30-10/1 1988 (Box 4)
    - Denmark 9=1 – 5 (Box 4)
    - Denver – Taiwan (Box 4)
    - Design History Society London (Box 4)
    - Design Horizons (Box 4)
    - Design Management Institute (Box 4)
    - Design Management Reference Materials, Notes (Box 4)
    - D – General (Box 4)
    - Dictionary of Art (Box 4)
    - Douglas, Kelly (Box 4)
    - Dynamics of Italian Design (Box 4)
    - Education (Box 4)
    - Edwards, Sandra (Box 4)
    - Ekuan (Box 4)
    - England (Box 4)
    - Erie Canal Museum (Box 4)
    - Everson (Box 4)
    - Everson 2 (Box 4)
    - Everson Board Minutes (Box 4)
    - Everson Projects (Box 4)
    - F - General (Box 5)
    - Finland (Box 5)
    - Fleet Bank Pay by Phone (Box 5)
    - Flinchum, Russell (Box 5)
    - France (Box 5)
    - Gallery Association (Box 5)
    - General (Box 5)
    - Germany (Box 5)
    - Graham Foundation (Box 5)
    - Greece (Box 5)
    - H - General (Box 5)
    - Haddon, Bob (Box 5)
    - Hagley (Box 5)
    - Hudson River Museum (Box 5)
    - Hong Kong (Box 5)
    - Hungary (Box 5)
    - ICSID 91-95 (Box 5)
    - ICSID 1994 (Box 5)
    - ICSID 1995 (Box 5)
    - ICSID '95 Taipei (Box 5)
    - ICSID General (Box 5)
    - ICSID General Assembly Minutes 22-23 Oct. 1988 (Box 5)
    - ID Contracts (Box 6)
    - India (Box 6)
    - India 2 (Box 6)
    - International Interior Design (Box 6)
    - Israel (Box 6)
    - Italy (Box 6)
    - J (Box 6)
    - Jerry, Michael (Box 6)
    - Jerry, Mike (Box 6)
    - Katona Gallery (Box 6)
    - K - General (Box 6)
    - Kodak (Box 6)
    - Korea (Box 6)
    - L - General (Box 6)
    - Lawrence, Peter (Box 6)
    - Loewy, Robert (Box 6)
    - Lord, Peter 1980-82 (Box 6)
    - M (Box 7)
    - Malaysia (Box 7)
    - Malmo (Box 7)
    - Manderfield, Elleh (Box 7)
    - Manlius Historical Society Calendar (Box 7)
    - Manifesto (Box 7)
    - Manitoba (Box 7)
    - Mann, Alexander (Box 7)
    - Maps (Box 7)
    - Margolin, V. (Box 7)
    - Matranga, V. (Box 7)
    - Mexico (Box 7)
    - Michigan (Box 7)
    - Misha-Black, Joan (Box 7)
    - Misha-Black Memorial Award (Box 7)
    - MIT Press (Box 7)
    - N - General (Box 7)
    - N+A (Box 7)
    - NEA (Box 7)
    - NEA Proposed Grant (Box 7)
    - Nelson, George (Box 7)
    - Netherlands (Box 7)
    - Norway (Box 7)
    - Ohio State University (Box 8)
    - Philadelphia (Box 8)
    - PIRKL (Box 8)
    - Poland (Box 8)
    - Portugal (Box 8)
    - Project USSR Exn/I.D. Educ in USA 1972 (Box 8)
    - Pulos Design Associates Inc. (Box 8)
    - R (Box 8)
    - R - General (Box 8)
    - Reilly (Box 8)
    - Renwick Gallery (Box 8)
    - Rhode Island School of Design (Box 8)
    - RIT EXIT 1982 (1990) (Box 8)
    - Rumania (Box 8)
    - Scandinavia (Box 8)
    - Schools (Box 8)
    - Silver (Box 8)
    - Singapore (Box 8)
    - Smithsonian (Box 8)
    - Soloviev (Box 8)
    - South Africa (Box 8)
    - Spain (Box 8)
    - Spilman (Box 8)
    - Spilman, Ray (Box 8)
    - St. James Press (Box 8)
    - Stickley Arts and Crafts Fund (Box 8)
    - Stone Quarry Hill A.P. (Box 8)
    - Stone Quarry Hill Art Park (Box 8)
    - Stumpf, William (Box 9)
    - Sweden (Box 9)
    - Switzerland (Box 9)
    - Syracuse City (Box 9)
    - Syracuse Parks and Recreation Billing 1983 (Box 9)
    - Syracuse University 1991 (Box 9)
    - Taiwan (Box 9)
    - Telephone Correspondence (Box 9)
    - Travel (Box 9)
    - U - General (Box 9)
    - United Nations (Box 9)
    - University of Chicago Press (Box 9)
    - University of Montreal Canada ID Review (Box 9)
    - University of Montreal Reviews of New Programs (Box 9)
    - U.S. Government (Box 9)
    - V - General (Box 9)
    - W - General (Box 9)
    - Who's Who (Box 9)
    - Yerewan (Box 9)
    - Yugoslavia (Box 9)
    - Zagorski (Box 9)
    - Zarganis (Box 9)
    - Z - General (Box 9)
    - 1963 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence Miscellaneous (Not filed) (Box 10)
  - Pulos Design Associates Office Records
    - Ron Yarblow Graphic Archives "Things" Binder (Box 11)
    - Singer Sewing Machine Correspondence 1985 (Box 11)
    - Photographs/ Extra for American Design Associates Adventure Arranged by Subjects (Box 11)
    - Pulos Design Associates – Photos (Box 11)
    - Binder – Product Design Slides (Box 11)
    - Singer Interview (Box 11)
    - PDA Folder (Box 11)
    - Resumes (Box 11)
    - List of Conferences, Lectures and Seminars (Box 11)
    - List of Pulos Publications (Box 11)
    - Client Listing (Box 11)
    - ADE 7/3 (photos and prints) (Box 12)
    - ADA Ch. 2 (Ills. 69-83 pgs. 96-107) (Box 12)
    - ADA Ch. 9 (Ills. 331-337 (a), pgs. 363-391) (Box 12)
    - ADA Ch. 9 sect. 1 & 2 (Ill. 338-357, pgs. 393-413) (Box 12)
    - 3 Binders (Box 13)
    - 1 Binder Design Slides (Box 13)
    - 1 Binder Syracuse Industrial Design Seminar Series (Box 13)
    - American Craft Magazines Oct. 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 14)
    - Craft Horizon Aug. 1953, Sept.-Oct 1964, Feb. 1965 (Box 14)
    - Department of Design Annual Report (1971) (Box 14)
    - 1971 Seminar Series – The State of the Art and the Science of Design (Box 14)
    - Metalsmith Magazine (Box 14)
    - The Sweet Heart and Others (Box 14)
    - Wurlitzer Info. (Box 14)
    - Articles- Crafts (Box 14)
    - 1976-1977 Onondagan (Box 14)
    - Material from Lazo Margan (Mexico) (Box 14)
    - ADA Index (Box 15)
    - Epilogue (Box 15)
    - Epilogue (Box 15)
    - Transportation "Water" (Box 15)
    - Transportation MS and DO (Box 15)
    - Autos (Box 15)
    - Automobile Safety (Box 15)
    - Private Cars – Transportation (Box 15)
    - Transportation – Public (Box 15)
    - Transportation – Private (Box 15)
    - Transportation – Land (Box 15)
    - Binder-Paul F. Delmerico (Slide Description List) (Box 16)
    - Binder-Pulos Design Associates – Records of Incorporation, Stocks, Notes On (Box 16)
    - Binder- Share Holders Meeting (Box 16)
    - Binder-Unmarked – Design Slides (Box 16)
    - Binder-"Washington USA 1986 – Post War ID" – (Slide Description List) – Design Slides (Box 16)
    - Binder-Illustration Graphics –Slides (Box 16)
    - Binder-Design Slides (Box 16)
    - Binder-Design Slides (Box 16)
    - Binder-"Background" – Design Slides (Box 16)
    - Binder – PDA "DC" (Box 17)
    - Binder – PDA "SBS-WE" (Box 17)
    - Photo Album "China?" (Box 17)
    - Company Logos – Paper Board (Box 18)
    - Alexander (Box 19)
    - Alexander/Alexander (Box 19)
    - Cryotec (Box 19)
    - UL CSA Marks (Box 19)
    - Elston Electronics (Box 19)
    - Emhart – EMI (Box 19)
    - EM1A (Box 19)
    - EM2 – Paul Scott (Box 19)
    - Erie Canal Museum (Box 19)
    - GBC – General Consulting (Box 19)
    - Pass and Seymour (Box 19)
    - 1984 Pass and Seymour (Box 19)
    - 1986 Seymour (Box 19)
    - 1984 Ridge Tool (Box 19)
    - Rockwell Contract (Box 19)
    - Rockwell Contract (Box 19)
    - Rubbermaid v. Contico (Box 19)
    - SUID John Thomas (Box 19)
    - Urinary Device (Box 19)
    - Welch-Allyn (Box 19)
    - Dictaphone (Box 19)
    - Alexander (Box 19)
    - Cryomech (Box 19)
    - Emhart (Box 19)
    - General Building Corp. (Box 19)
    - Sources GBL (Box 19)
    - GBL (Box 19)
    - GBL 1989 (Box 19)
    - GB 30F8 (Box 19)
    - Visit to Rockwell April 1968 (Box 19)
    - I.D. Magazine (Box 20)
    - Design Publication (Box 20)
    - Building and Building Painting (Box 20)
    - Building Painting (Box 20)
    - PDA General (Box 20)
    - PDA Employment Agreement (Box 20)
    - Promotional Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Public Relations (Box 20)
    - PDA Accounting (Box 20)
    - Cancelled Checks (Box 20)
    - American Express (Box 20)
    - Petty Cash — Office (Box 20)
    - Jim Brown Travel service (Box 20)
    - Dermudy, Burke and Brown (Box 20)
    - Div Type Inc. (Box 20)
    - Dues + Subscription Contributions (Box 20)
    - Eastern Copy Products (Box 20)
    - Estabrook Printing (Box 20)
    - Federal Express (Box 20)
    - Lyndon Office Park (Box 20)
    - MCI Telecommunications (Box 20)
    - Perry/ Spectrum Office Supply (Box 20)
    - 1986 Time Sheets (Box 20)
    - AJP + BJP Expenses Refunded (Box 20)
    - Syracuse Blue Print Company (Box 20)
    - Misc. Expenses (Box 20)
    - Reports — Disston — Piper (Box 21)
    - New Clients Development (Box 21)
    - PDA (Box 21)
    - Capris Unpaid Billing (Box 21)
    - Yearly Planning (Box 21)
    - Staff Training (Box 21)
    - PDA (Box 21)
    - PDA (Box 21)
    - Dictaphone Corporation (Box 21)
    - Pulos Design Associates (Box 21)
    - TR Binder -1950-1958 (Box 22)
    - PDA Correspondence (Box 22)
    - Folders (6) Photo lists, invoices, correspondence (Box 22)
    - Envelopes (3) articles, prints, photos (Box 22)
    - Black Notebook – Persons – Designers 1940-1942 (Box 22)
    - Black Notebook – Persons (Box 22)
    - Green Notebook – Persons – Designers 48-85 (Box 22)
    - Armco (Box 23)
    - Micro-Analog Associates (Bob Anderson) (Box 23)
    - 1984 Syr. Parks and Recreation Display Panel (Box 23)
    - Syracuse Parks and Recreation SY – 2 (Box 23)
    - Dictaphone Reports (Box 23)
    - Rockwell PDA Promo (Box 23)
    - Syr – 1 Display Panels (Box 23)
    - Syracuse Walking Tour (Box 23)
    - Dictaphone Reports (Box 23)
    - Rockwell PDA Promo Booklet (Box 23)
    - Sullivan County Comm. College (Box 23)
    - Syracuse University Billing (Box 23)
    - SU-12 SU Logo Society of Fellows (Box 23)
    - Image-Maker 1000/2000 Final Art/Int. (Box 23)
    - Northbrook Shredders GIB-GA (Box 23)
    - Northbrook Shredders – Negs of Final Art GB-GA (Box 23)
    - Personal Shredder (Box 23)
    - GB-8 Personal Shredder Final Art Paste Ups, Negs. (Box 23)
    - GB-GA 1065 Shreddermask Final Art (Box 23)
    - GBC-3 Graphics (Box 23)
    - PA–25 (Box 23)
    - PA–26 (Box 23)
    - Rubbermaid v. Cortico (Box 23)
    - GBC–4 (Box 23)
    - GBC–5 (Box 23)
    - GB–GC + GD Redo Sunbird (Box 23)
    - Final Art GB4/GB7 (Box 23)
    - GB4 / Control Panel Graphics (Box 23)
    - GBC Plastic Binder GBC Thermabind (Box 23)
    - GBC Shredmaster (Box 23)
    - B & W design photos (Box 24)
    - 5 "spectator" yearbooks (Box 24)
    - 3 empty checkbook covers (Box 24)
    - 10 Daybooks (Box 24)
    - Monthly schedules (in rubber bands) (Box 24)
    - Pulos office map (Box 24)
    - Business cards (Box 24)
    - PDA Office Records (Box 25)
    - Accounts 1980-1984 (Box 25)
    - Check Receipts (Box 25)
    - 1985 PDA Receipts (Box 25)
  - Pulos Research Notes for Books and Articles
    - Reference Material EL Archiving (Notes) (Box 26)
    - 121 J (Box 26)
    - 1 Box Unmarked (Notes) (Box 26)
    - Philosophy (Box 27)
    - Theory/General (Box 27)
    - Essays Theory (Box 27)
    - Products (Box 27)
    - Chapter 1 A MS (Box 28)
    - Basement Important (Reference Material and Notes) 1 Box Unmarked (Box 28)
    - Philosophy 1965 – (Box 28)
    - Practice 1951-1970 (Box 28)
    - Transportation –Autos 1965 (Box 29)
    - Transportation – Autos 1945-64 (Box 29)
    - Automobiles 1940-45 (Box 29)
    - Chapter 8 Section 2 (Box 29)
    - Product Lists (Box 29)
    - Power and Garden Tools Chapter 8 (Box 29)
    - Machines Chapter 8 – Section 2 (Box 29)
    - Medicine (Box 29)
    - Product Chapter 8 (Box 29)
    - Products (Box 29)
    - Products/Communication Research and Rough Chapter 8 (Box 29)
    - Graphics References General (Box 29)
    - Plastics (Box 29)
    - Appliances (Box 29)
    - Products Chapter 2 Data Disk/Research (Box 29)
    - Photograph/Film Chapter 8 (Box 29)
    - Chapter 8 Sound and Image (Box 29)
    - Machines Business (Box 29)
  - Everson Museum and Syracuse University
    - S.U. I.D. (Box 30, Folder A)
    - Shuttle Medal – S.U. I.D. 4/67 (Box 30, Folder A)
    - Curriculum Planning (Box 30, Folder A)
    - S.U. (Box 30, Folder A)
    - Everson Board 1986 (Box 30, Folder B)
    - Everson Museum Trustee 1987 (Box 30, Folder B)
    - Everson Trustees 1988-89 (Box 30, Folder B)
    - Everson Trustees 1990-91 (Box 30, Folder B)
    - A & E Minutes (Box 30, Folder C)
    - Design Practice (Box 30, Folder C)
    - Proflega (Box 30, Folder C)
    - Tarrytown Seminar – Oct. 1974 (Box 31)
    - ADA Printouts (Box 31)
    - Design Magazine Photocopies (Box 32)
    - IDSA Archives (Box 32)
    - Archives NHPRC (Box 32)
    - (Elastic ) Mexico A.C. Margan (Box 32)
  - Norman Bel Geddes
    - Photos, papers, designs, newspaper clippings (not organized) (Box 33)
    - Norman Bel Geddes Theatre Collection (Box 33)
    - 2 Industrial Design Magazines "Bel Geddes" (Box 33)
    - Bel Geddes Slides (14) (Box 33)
  - ICSID
    - ICSID Maxwell Prize (Box 34)
    - ICSID 1988-89 (Box 34)
    - Interviews 1951-1957 (Box 34)
  - IDSA & ICSID
    - IDSA Central NY (Box 35)
    - IDSA (Box 35)
    - Newsletters IDSA (Box 35)
    - IDAC (Box 35)
    - IDAC (Box 35)
    - ICSID Board 1993-5 (Box 35)
    - IFI (Box 35)
    - ICSID 1993 (Box 35)
    - ICSID Board Meeting June '93 (Box 35)
    - ICSID (Box 35)
    - ICSID Book (Box 35)
    - ICSID 1994 (Box 35)
    - ICSID Glasgow 1993 (Box 35)
    - ICSID Corr. 1991 (Box 35)
    - Icograda (Box 35)
  - Box unmarked
    - File: IDSA/ KRUPS July 1986 (Box 36)
    - File: IDSA 1986 (Box 36)
    - File: Manuscripts (Box 36)
    - File IDI (Box 36)
    - File: Syracuse Correspondence 1983-1989 (Box 36)
  - Asia
    - Korea (Box 37)
    - Japan Nano (Box 37)
    - Japan Design Foundation (Box 37)
    - Japan 1990 (Box 37)
    - Hiroshima Culture and Economic Relevance of Design (Box 37)
    - Japan Design Foundation – 4th Annual 1988-1989 (Box 37)
    - Japan Design Foundation – 15th Award 1982-1985 (Box 37)
    - Equality by Design KSID '89 Nagoya (Box 37)
    - Takashi Nagata – Japan (Box 37)
    - Japan 1987-1989 (Box 37)
    - Japan 1975-1986 (Box 37)
    - Japan Design Foundation 6th Competition 1963 (Box 37)
    - Japan Design Foundation 1986-1987 (Box 37)
    - Japan Design Foundation 1984-1985 (Box 37)
    - Chinese Student Thesis (Box 38)
    - China Background Material (Box 38)
    - China 89-90 (Box 38)
    - Educt. Shanghai May 1991 (Box 38)
    - China (Box 38)
    - Genl. Correspondence China (Box 38)
    - Yang Jan Cai Jun China (Box 38)
    - Tong Ji University (Box 38)
    - Shanghai (Box 38)
    - PRC 1987-1990 (Box 38)
    - People's Republic of China 1984-1988 (Box 38)
    - PRC 1991 (Box 38)
    - PRC 1991 Wuhan Oct. (Box 38)
    - PRC 1992 (Box 38)
    - PRC 1993 NO China Trip (Box 38)
    - PRC 1994-1995 (Box 38)
  - Articles, lectures and seminars
    - American Craft 3/1998 – Symposium Report (Box 39)
    - Type Form and the Designer – Danish Design Center 9/2/93 (Box 39)
    - For the Record A.M. Craftsmen & Magazine May 1993 (Box 39)
    - Manuscript Review/ U. of Chicago Press 3 May 1993 (Box 39)
    - Misha Black Medal 9/14/93 (Box 39)
    - Visions and Echoes RSA 1993 (Box 39)
    - Tallon Testimonial July 26, 1993 (Box 39)
    - Manuscript Review 8/93 (Box 39)
    - ICOGADA Sept. 1993/Welcome/ICSSD (Box 39)
    - History of Product Design (Box 39)